intercom.com 2017-05-12

# Privacy

We at Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom," “we," “us," “our") know that our users (“you," “your") care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes how Intercom, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Website: [intercom.com](https://www.intercom.com/)/[intercom.io](https://www.intercom.io/). Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the Website or Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. Any capitalized terms used herein without definition shall have the meaning given to them in the Intercom Terms of Use.

Intercom, Inc. complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Please refer to Addendum 1.1 of this policy for more information regarding Intercom, Inc.’s EU Privacy Shield Certification Information.

## What does this privacy policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website or Services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our [Terms of Use](https://docs.intercom.com/pricing-and-terms/terms)). No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services.

## What information does Intercom collect?

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to personalize and improve the Services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for the Services, to analyze how users utilize the Website, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (described in this Section and in Section C below). We collect the following types of information:

### A. Information You Provide to Us:

Your Personal Information: We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, we collect Personal Information such as your name, email address, and browser information. You can choose not to provide us with certain information such as your credit card information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you cannot be individually identified, and provide that information to our partners.

Your Customers' Personal Information: In order to provide you with the Services, we also receive and store any information you choose to provide us with respect to your customers (“End User Customers"). The End User Customer information (“End User Customer Information") we receive and store typically includes names and email addresses of your customers, but will consist of any information you choose to provide us with.

Upon sign up, if you choose to ask a friend to install intercom for you, we will ask for your friend's email address to notify him of such a request. Intercom, Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email notification.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Intercom, Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### B. Information Collected Automatically:

Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, “cookie" information, and the page you requested. “Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Website are visited by you. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our Website's features. If you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you.

When you visit the Website, whether as an Intercom customer or a non-registered user just browsing, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data"). For example, Log Data may include information such as your computer's IP address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Website and the Services and for the Website's technical administration, to increase our Website's functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors' needs.

Additionally, as part of our provision of the Services to you, if you install certain software code provided by us on your website, we will also track and collect End User Customer usage information on your website. We also use third parties to collect publicly available information relating to your End User Customers. For more information on how we collect and compile End User Customer Information, please see Section C below.

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, scripts and tags are used by Intercom Inc. and our third party partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking users’ movements around the site, and gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing these types of tracking technologies.

We use Local Shared Objects, such as Flash cookies, and Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use Flash cookies to collect and store information. You can manage Flash cookies [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

Our third party partners also employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do [not] tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personal information.

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt out of cookies [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) (or if located in the European Union, opt out [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

### C. E-mail and Other Communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may communicate with you about your use of the Website or Services. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by adjusting the settings on your account screen in the Website. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com).

## Where do we store your personal information?

If you are located outside the United States, the information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored and processed at, a destination in the United States. By submitting information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Is the personal information secure?

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

When you enter your information on our site we encrypt the transmission of that information using transport layer security (TLS).

The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site's privacy policy.

## What personal information can I access?

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you've provided to us:

  * name and password
  * email address
  * profile photo
  * company name
  * position in company
  * location
  * credit card information

The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Website changes. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com).

#### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from Testimonials or comments please contact us at [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com).

## What choices do I have?

You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features. You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in Section C above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. You may request deletion of your account by contacting us at [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com). Please note that some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements but barring legal requirements, we will delete your information within 90 days. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Changes to this privacy policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes or changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email prior to the change becoming effective. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted.

## Questions or concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message team@intercom.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Intercom, Inc. 55 2nd St, 4th Fl., San Francisco, CA 94105 USA

Effective Date: September 21, 2016

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [team@intercom.com](mailto:team@intercom.com). If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please [contact](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge).

## Addendum – 1.1 Intercom Inc. EU Privacy Shield Certification Information

### EU-US Privacy Shield Certification

The following information aligns Intercom, Inc. Privacy Statement with the specific points required by the Privacy Shield self-certification process, and ensures Intercom, Inc.’s compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework.

Intercom, Inc. complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Intercom, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, visit [privacyshield.gov](http://privacyshield.gov/).

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Intercom, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact the dedicated Intercom, Inc. compliance team at:

Intercom, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers](http://bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers) for more information and to file a complaint.

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

Intercom, Inc. is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

### US-Swiss Safe Harbor

Intercom, Inc. complies with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Switzerland. Intercom, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the US-Swiss Safe Harbor and to view our certification page, please visit [export.gov/safeharbor/swiss](http://export.gov/safeharbor/swiss).

In compliance with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Intercom, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Intercom, Inc. at:

Intercom, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-Swiss Safe Harbor to an independent dispute resolution mechanism operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.

### Organization Information

Intercom, Inc. 55 2nd Street, 4th Floor, San Francisco, California, 94105

### Organization Contact

Valid individual within Intercom, Inc. handling of complaints, access requests, and any other issues concerning Intercom, Inc.’s compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework:

Niall Sheridan, Engineering Manager, [compliance@intercom.com](mailto:compliance@intercom.com)

### Organization Corporate Officer

Certifying Intercom, Inc. compliance with the Privacy Shield Framework:

By submitting this self-certification, the below listed corporate officer attests that he/she is authorized to submit the self-certification on behalf of your organization and all entities or subsidiaries indicated below.

Ciaran Lee, CTO, [compliance@intercom.com](mailto:compliance@intercom.com)

### Intercom, Inc. subsidiaries also adhering to the Privacy Shield Principles

Intercom R&D Unlimited Company (an Irish Company)

### Types of information covered by Intercom, Inc’s Privacy Policy

Human Resources Data refers to personal data about employees, past or present, collected in the context of the employment relationship. Information other than Human Resources data includes the following: customer, client, visitor, and clinical trial data.

Intercom, Inc’s Privacy Policy covers: Personal data other than human resources data.

### Purposes for which Intercom, Inc. collects and processes personal data in reliance on the Privacy Shield

Please refer to Section “What information does Intercom collect?” of this Privacy Policy.

In particular, and regarding the disclosure of your Personal Data, please refer to Section “Will Intercom share any of the personal information it receives?” of this Privacy Policy.

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, Intercom, Inc. is potentially liable.

### User’s right to access their data

Intercom, Inc. acknowledges that EU individuals have the right to access the personal information that we maintain about them. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his query to [compliance@intercom.com](mailto:compliance@intercom.com). If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

Please refer to Section “What personal information can I access?” to find out about how to access, correct or delete your Personal Data.

Please refer to Section “What choices do I have?” to find out about the choices and means available to you to limit use and disclosure of your Personal Data.

Location of Intercom, Inc.’s privacy policy applicable to personal data covered under Intercom, Inc.’s self-certification:

  * Effective Date: September 21, 2016
  * Intercom, Inc. Privacy Policy: [docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/intercom-inc-privacy-policy](https://docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/intercom-inc-privacy-policy)
  * EU Privacy Shield Addendum: [docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/intercom-inc-privacy-policy](https://docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/intercom-inc-privacy-policy)

Federal Trade Commission will serve as the statutory body and has jurisdiction to investigate claims against Intercom, Inc. regarding possible unfair or deceptive practices and violations of laws or regulations covering privacy.
